# Fadi Barhoum **Full Stack Web Developer**

Dubai, UAE | (+971) 50 770 4776 | Male | 07/06/1993 |

en.fadi.barhoum@gmail.com | fadi-barhoum.github.io/ | linkedin.com/in/fadi-barhoum

### **Summary**

With over six years of experience, I balance business goals with technology requirements, quickly learning new skills to enhance both my expertise and the value I bring to the business. My focus is always on delivering the best outcomes for projects and companies.

# **Work Experience**

### Elite WhereGO - Dubai, UAE **Full Stack Web Developer**

04/2024 - Present

- Developing dedicated pages integrated with the mobile app backend, allowing users to access all mobile app features directly from the website. Both the mobile and web apps currently offer 12 services, with more to be added.
- Developed a responsive, high-performance website showcasing all relevant company information for partners, riders, and users, optimized for SEO.

Freelancer 01/2018 - 01/2024

### Full Stack Web Developer

- Collaborated with clients to define project goals and deliver custom web
- Developed responsive, high-performance web interfaces optimized for
- Developed scalable databases.
- Wrote detailed technical documentation.

## Masar Syria – Damascus, Syria **Full Stack Web Developer**

01/2021 - 03/2022

- Collaborated with clients to define project goals and deliver custom web
- Developed responsive, high-performance web interfaces optimized for
- Developed scalable databases.
- Wrote detailed technical documentation.

#### Charitable Society for Sustainable Development – 09/2019 - 04/2023Damascus, Syria

### **Software Developer**

- Developed and implemented software solutions.
- Proactive identification and implementation of technical solutions led to an 80% increase in work efficiency.
- Produced detailed software documentation to support ongoing development and user training.
- Rigorously safeguards organizational digital assets and data.

# **Education**

**Information Technology - Software Engineering** 

2012 - 2018

Damascus University

#### Certificates

# **Skills**

Laravel | WordPress | PHP | JavaScript | jQuery | MySQL | CSS | HTML | APIs | Rest APIs | Git | E-Payment | Responsive Design | Bootstrap | Cross-Browser Compatibility | SEO Optimization | Performance Optimization Debugging and Troubleshooting

#### **Soft Skills**

Teamwork | Leadership | Problemsolving | Time management | Creativity | Adaptability | Attention to Detail | Critical Thinking | Decision-Making | Project Management | Client Relationship Management

### Languages

Arabic (Native) English (Professional proficiency)

### Activities

#### The Sacred Hearts Society

Damascus, Syria 01/2019 - 01/2024

- Social Worker
  - Caseworker 0
    - Volunteer

#### **GOPA-DERD**

Damascus, Syria 11/2019 - 02/2022

Volunteer

## **Charitable Society for Sustainable** Development

Damascus, Syria 04/2016 - 08/2019

Volunteer